5,4,3,2,1
Thank you!
It's been a year since the Great East
Japan Earthquake.
So, it's been a year since the
earthquake.
Wow, that's amazing.
The earthquake was a year ago.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Aya ・IKIMOTO・SAء
Look at this!
Oh wait,yelling at my spokesman Ahh
This program is a program where six
people who are active to promote
something exciting challenge various
things to raise the excitement level in
the world.
I will prove the exciting future.
Happy New Day
Lion sing
Good morning.
It's morning.
We're going to start the first
shooting.
We're going to shoot for Tomorrow's
Strongest.
It's been a while since we wore this
costume.
I think my skirt got shorter.
The color of the skirt is cute.
The makeup artist made it for me.
It's a mixture of red and pink.
What color is it?
This umbrella is not broken.
It's broken today.
This is the newest umbrella.
It's scary.
I want an umbrella like Hiori.
I'll do it.
I can fold it easily.
Isn't it amazing?
Really?
Thank you for watching.
My favorite is castella.
Oh, castella.
I ate it before.
It's before the concert.
I might eat it all before the concert.
Today is a toast.
All members of the group ate it.
I didn't support them.
The members right before acoustic
version will be announced next Subscribe
to our main channel Toku- yoshizawa
What?
No!
What should I do?
But, if I pull this
Here we go
It's the first time I've ever turned
this
I'm glad
It's here
Thank you
I'm tired.
It's orange.
Is it spinning?
The best baseball star,
Ozawa Tenkomori
Magic show
Inside Kia Hiroshi
Let's have a party!
Let's all get together and make a big
deal out of it!
If we all work together,
we can make a huge splash at the jungle
tower!
Let's go!
Happy New Year!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Happy New Year!
We've finished the re-construction of
the tomorrow.
We've finished the construction of the
merry-go-round.
We're going to play with water guns and
buckets.
I've been caught by a fisherman.
I want to do that, but I'm sorry I
can't.
We're on the side of the cameraman.
We're not caught.
I want to do it again.
We used to play with buckets.
I saw a lot of videos.
I really want to do it.
We're going to play with water guns and
buckets.
I'm going to shoot the second one.
It's going to be on soon.
I'm going to shoot it quickly.
It's hot.
Look at this.
I'm going to shoot the second one.
Hello! I'm a watermelon.
I'm a dolphin.
I'm going to eat a watermelon.
I want to eat a watermelon.
Do you want to eat a watermelon?
Yes, I do.
Watermelon.
It's cute.
It's fun.
That's amazing.
I'm so happy!
I'll sharpen the sense of direction I
want to take
I'll pretend nothing's wrong and walk
in front of you
Hurry up and say something
Maybe everything is my misunderstanding
I'm not going to let go of our memories
It's too early to give up on a no-side
Cut the best of the best
A little bit of kindness is important
It's so good!
Is that sweat?
Yes, it's sweat!
I'm a professional dancer!
I'm wet!
It was fun!
I'm sweating a lot!
It's a good sound!
It's started!
I'm going to hit you!
I was hit!
You haven't been hit by Aki-chan yet.
I got hit for the first time!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Looks delicious! I want to eat it!
Oh, it's cute!
It's a water gun!
You can't shoot it!
I was told that I wanted to shoot a
bubble gun.
What?
Bubble gun! Bubble gun!
Eye! Eye!
Mouth! Mouth! Mouth!
I shot a bubble gun!
Oh, it's cute!
Bubble gun! Bubble gun!
It's cute! Bubble gun!
Oh, you look energetic today!
I felt summer!
Summer!
I didn't feel summer this year.
There are many people!
I'm so happy that I can't stop crying.
I'm going to buy a juice on Wednesday.
I'm going to buy an ice cream on
Wednesday.
Welcome!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Oh my God!
It's raining heavily
The main propagation source of second-
hand cars is the desert
Hmm
Watch this!
Let's extend this war!
We're back to the second day.
We shot the night bus.
We did a live broadcast.
We're going to shoot again.
From Gyojimae to Gyojimae.
We'll do our best!
I think I'll like it.
It's nice to be in it.
It's cute.
We're in Gyojimae at night.
It's so beautiful.
It's so beautiful at night.
It's so beautiful. I'm getting
emotional.
I'm so sad.
It's so easy to sleep.
Thank you for watching.
Let's get high and go for the top
Physical strength, girl power, number
one, I'll take the top
Ah everybody's a Lotte boy
Dig patterns
The next is high-level
Please
I'm so excited.
I'm spinning.
I'm so excited that I can fly in the
sky.
What?
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you for watching.
Shimokuha does mind games like kids'
games for their current mood.
WAITING FOR LINE
Wait for its APP estification lottery
and you might be gone!
The flag is WOOKZ's favorite!
He won't play for a while!
Attemps to use his card.
You might be missing something.
GAMEDAY
The fireworks are waiting!
We can see the lights!
Yup, we can!
The fireworks
If you're stuck next to me, I'm not
giving up!
I sit and watch as the fire
extinguishes
Each times the wind blows, the
fragrance of love hangs around
The shadows that I talked to a lot
about grow so long
I wonder if I want to go home soon
I'm happy just to be able to meet you.
I'm happy to be able to spend time like
this.
A rainbow-colored adventure.
It won't change forever.
I've been waiting for you.
My hair is getting longer.
I wonder if you want to go home.
I love you.
I fell in love with fate and fulfilled
my long-standing dream
I'm sure I can do anything, even though
I have no basis
Thank you very much!
It should be like that,
like that traffic light thing.
Let's go together, everyday is the
strongest day!
Let's go! Tomorrow, Tomorrow, Tomorrow,
the strongest day!
Hello, hello to the new me!
It doesn't matter what they say,
I'll just keep going!
Tomorrow, Tomorrow, Tomorrow, the
strongest day!
Hello, hello to the infinite
possibilities!
Challenge everything you want to do!
Prove the future that will never be
broken!
Ah! Happy New Day!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Together, Tomorrow is the strongest
day!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Together, Tomorrow is the strongest
day!
If you reflect on yourself every day,
you'll grow every day
There will come a time when you think
everything has a meaning
Even if it's not a love of fate, even
if it's not a dream
If you can hit it with all your might
and learn even one thing
It's honesty!
Look at it with long eyes, there's no
failure
It's a good job to be laughed at
We can't use our hearts, we can!
We want to be the strongest again!
Oh no!
Tumor, tumor, tumor, the strongest!
Hello, hello to a wonderful world!
It doesn't matter how difficult the
story is
I'm just excited to be alive!
Tumor, tumor, tumor, the strongest!
Hello, hello to an unexpected
encounter!
Let's live with a smile for now
Thank you, water and sweet potatoes!
Happy victory!
Let's charge our power together!
Let's clap our hands together!
If we put our hearts together
We'll shout out with super full power!
Genki. Ma. To. Ya.
Yuuki. Ma. To.
Genki. Ma. To.
Yuuto. Ma. To.
Aichou. Ma. To.
Tanshou. Ma. To.
Tanshou!